Just a short walk away
It looks like Kulebia-san is there too.
Like this.
He's got an Abima!
Hello everyone, this time I'd like to share with you how our members spent New Year's.
I'd like to share with you how we spent New Year's. We did it last year.
I'm like, "That's me.
You're like last year. I guess so.
Nagiha, I was more active during New Year's than ever before.
So I'm looking forward to making a video that you can enjoy with me.
I hope we can make a video that you can enjoy together.
I'm sure everyone is spending their New Year's in different ways, so please enjoy watching.
And here we go.
Hello everyone!
I'm Iroha Kyokuta, of NAGIBOKA 46 Gokisei!
I'm Iroha Kyokuta!
Good night!
I'm off on New Year's Day.
I said I wanted to ride the baby carriage.
We're here to go baby carriage riding as a family.
The beginning of life...
It's so much fun, isn't it?
I'm going to watch and move on.
I'll do it!
So fun!
Here we are at Kumamoto Castle.
Kumamoto Castle.
Wow!
It's so big!
I went up to the claws!
Amazing!
It was great!
Clear sky
Clear skies.
It can be strong
It's hot
I went up there with my sympathy
Next is the same as the staff
It was a live job.
Let's be honest. There's only one thing we're not doing.
I like you. I like you. I like you.
La la la la la la...
Finally, I'm not being honest.
Yes, ma'am.
Hello. I'm Kakihara Kou.
We've been going to high school together since middle school.
We've been friends since middle school through high school, and we're still friends today.
It was her birthday.
I'm drawing a picture to give to her.
I'm drawing on my iPad.
This is how I drew it.
This is my friend's guess.
I hope she will be happy.
It's such a New Year's drawing!
My New Year's Day is
Happy New Year!
Hello! My name is Mayu Tamura.
The year 2024 has begun, so I bought this cat tower for my cats,
I am going to assemble this now and let the cats play with it to their heart's content.
I'll do my best!
OK!
OK, Whitgo!
Do you want me to bring a model?
Yes, sir.
Do not push the handle.
Yes, please don't push.
Please do not push the handles.
I don't have any money.
I'll take it.
Yes, sir.
Are you ready?
One, two, three, go!
Five.
Six.
Seven.
Eight.
Nine.
Hello, my name is Miyu Matsuwa.
It's my birthday and I turned 20 years old!
My family prepared balloons and stuff for me.
Yes!
Now that I'm an adult, I'm going to have my first drink.
I'm going to have my first drink!
I'm going home now to toast with my mom.
Cheers.
Red wine.
Bon appétit!
Thank you for watching.
That's it.
I'm going to grow up.
I'll do my best
Hello, this is Yukino
How did you spend New Year's Day?
I went to an empty shrine I found when I was taking a walk
No one there
That's right
I wish you all a happy new year!
Thank you for watching!
Happy New Year!
I'm here at my grandma's house right now.
I've finished my participation day for a bit
We've finished eating Osechi (New Year's dishes)
I'd like to have a hand-rolled sushi party today
And for lunch today, my grandma
She made my favorite coya tofu hamburger steak and chicken cutlet
and chicken cutlet, which is my favorite!
I'm not sure if I'll be able to eat enough hand-rolled sushi
I'm going to eat a lot of sushi!
What did you want to eat?
That's right.
I came to eat beef buns.
It's my only friend from my hometown.
Hi. - Hi.
I'm here with my mother.
It's like All Made in Japan.
You're talking about that?
We were.
Bon appétit.
Is it good?
Yes, it's good.
It is, isn't it?
Thank you for your hard work.
Yes, this is Kimi from Tsukaguchi. What a surprise to find me here in Korea.
It's still very cold with snow on the ground.
I will enjoy New Year fully.
I am Miku Ichinose of Nogizaka46.
I came to eat delicious squid with my family today.
Yes, I am an adult this year.
I would like to make this year a year to grow up a little bit more than last year.
I look forward to working with you all this year!
Take care of yourself!
Happy New Year!
Happy New Year! I'm Aya Ogawa.
I went to cheer for the Halcon Valley on New Year's Day.
We wore matching T-shirts, held balloons and cheered a lot!
It was really cool to see them chase after the ball until the end without giving up!
It was really cool!
I was there and was so moved and encouraged to do my best.
This year, I want to do my best with even higher aspirations. I look forward to working with you this year, Flower Seventeen!
Hello, my name is Satsuki Sugawara.
I dyed my hair today.
I dyed it dark.
I also went out to dinner with Shizuki Yamashita from Sakurazaka 46.
We just finished eating.
She's so cute!
I've already made a move on her.
She's cute. I'd like to get to know her better.
Thank you for your hard work.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Minako Kuro, a 4th year student at Morisaka University.
I am a member of the baseball club
I'm a member of the Morisaka baseball club, and I'm here to play a baseball game with the members of the Morisaka baseball club.
I'm learning baseball in my physical education class at school
I'm learning to play baseball in PE class at school, and I've been getting very good grades.
I've been hitting mostly pet balls and par balls.
I went to the batting center to try my best to get a hit.
Please watch coach Mackie.
I'll do my best.
Music
I'm waiting for your advice and supportive comments!
Hello everyone, this is Reno Nakamura.
How did you spend New Year's?
Can you tell by looking at it?
I've just been on a Harry Potter studio tour!
Yes, and Rose, too!
We're doing the Seven Clauses today!
Yes, yes...
Well, we're only at the halfway point.
We're having a lot of fun with magic and stuff.
We're having a lot of fun!
Happy New Year!
I'm carrying out the challenge of not stepping out of my house on New Year's Day.
I ate spicy food at home on January 2nd.
I had a stomach ache after eating spicy food at home on January 2nd.
Now I can only eat rice porridge
I can only eat soft foods like rice porridge.
My stomach hurts.
It hurts.
Hello, my name is Teresa Ikeda.
Let me tell you what I'm buried in right now,
Actually, it's a doll, a stuffed animal, that I made myself.
What I made it with is this, originally fluffy cotton.
Wool felt. If you use a three-pronged needle like this and prick prick prick, the cotton gradually hardens and you can make a very cute doll.
Here they are. Isn't it big?
I hope you all get into handicrafts, too.
See you soon.
New Year's Day
Not Goo!
New Year's Day is
New Year's Day is not goo.
I'm spending New Year's with Mommy.
It's not goo, is it?
Goo!
I'm Rika Sato.
I was out with my family today.
We went for a walk.
And I recently bought a camera.
I took some pictures of the scenery with the camera.
Look at this!
There are a lot of ducks.
Do it!
Yes, sir.
Let's see what they look like.
I got a shot of a lot of ducks.
Let's say you don't need them.
Thank you for watching.
Hello, I'm Luna Hayashi, a fourth-year student.
Today is the coming-of-age ceremony.
I'm wearing a furisode to the coming-of-age ceremony.
I'm with my friends.
Yay!
I haven't seen my friends from junior high school for a long time.
I passed by many people.
I passed by a lot of people from elementary school.
I was surprised to find out that some of them were in my class in elementary school.
I thought I could recognize some of them.
Their faces...
It's going to be a day I'll remember for a long time.
Happy New Year!
Hey, please look at me.
Happy New Year 2024!
I see it...
Goat! Goat!
Goat!
Goat... Goat...
Happy New Year!
They came to sit on my lap today.
I didn't expect two of them.
I can't move.
Yes, so I've been playing with a lot of cats.
I will do my best in 2024.
Bye bye!
This is Narita Airport.
This is Seimi Alley.
Today, I'm going to take a bus from Narita Airport
We're going to a place.
This is it.
I didn't think you'd get out.
Oh!
Oh, wait.
He's looking right at us.
I don't think that's his hole.
It's right here on his head.
Oh!
Whoa!
Four engines.
Pretty.
This place looks pretty good.
Welcome back.
Chuck Rick.
We're done. I was here until the last minute.
Oh, you show Purikura.
I took purikura.
See?
It was fun.
Because the sunset was so beautiful.
Wow.
It's nice.
Good night.
I came to the aviation museum in Narita.
With Rei.
Nice to meet you too.
I'm Arno Nakanishi, 5th term student.
I went to Disneyland and Disney Sea with my classmates Hina Okamoto and Teresa Ikeda for New Year's.
We were so excited like we were back in the old days.
We had so much fun!
This is Yabomio on the 4th!
I'm wearing this oshiruko sweatshirt today.
I want to eat oshiruko!
I can't seem to even warm it up with liquid
I might have stuck it in my belly.
I'm sure you got the batteries dirty.
You soiled the batteries, and the container is really dirty.
Obviously, the umbrella.
Bye-bye.
I'm gonna go wipe the microwave.
I'm Ayano Yoshida, Christy.
I'm Reika Yamamoto.
I'm Renkanchi.
It's a New Year's party.
But we've finished eating.
We had the party we've always wanted to have.
I've already made it.
Shirin
Durun.
So many!
I don't think there are many people who make this much.
I'll eat it
I'd like to eat it.
Good night.
What?
Yeah, it's good.
It's good.
Yum.
Yum. Yum.
Come on.
Here it comes. Here it comes.
Leo, Kana and Perkina.
Come on. Come on.
There you go, kitty, kitty, kitty, kitty, kitty.
Nyan cat's name.
He doesn't like it.
Rucchan.
I don't like it.
He doesn't like it.
Let's end it.
Okay, bye-bye.
Hello.
Happy New Year!
I'm JM.
I'm in London.
I'm in London. The tree is still here.
I'm traveling alone.
There are many stores here.
It's so cute like this.
There's also a vintage clothing shop just a few steps away.
So I went here yesterday.
I came here yesterday.
So today is my first time to walk around the city.
I'm going to enjoy it.
And in the afternoon
I've made a reservation for Remisé, so I'm going to see it.
Look, it's the Tower Bridge!
This is what I wanted to see, so I'm glad I got to see it.
It's so beautiful!
Happy new year!
My name is Sakura Endo.
My New Year's Day is at home!
It's the only time I can stay at home like this during New Year's.
I found myself reading 3 books!
The one I'm reading right now is used.
And I got it on sale for 100 yen!
Bye!
I've really been doing bookmarks all over the place and losing them, so there's a receipt stuck in there instead. Sorry. I'll fix it.
I'm spending my New Year's Day visiting shrines, eating ozoni, and so on. Thank you very much for your continued support this year.
Thank you very much.
Good night.
I am Nagi Inoue. I am Takuro Kawasaki.
I am here in Kyoto.
I eat only useless end.
Yes, I'll have it.
I'm here.
Shimizu.
Hang in there!
Yes, Bon appétit!
Ta-da!
I'm here in Karuizawa!
Hehe...
There's a little something weird about the trainer's hand voice.
We are here on a trip to Karuizawa!
That's a long and stinky trip!
I hope it will be a good year for me too!
Today was the day of the seven herbs
We had the seven herbs, too!
They were delicious!
Such a trip is about traveling!
Ta-da!
It's really cold!
It's cold next to here, too.
Please continue.
Here you go.
We're in Karuizawa.
First time in Karuizawa.
And who's with me?
Oh?
He's here.
What?
That's amazing.
How is that possible?
Oh, my God.
Batty alone?
Yeah, I am.
I'm so happy.
Look at this.
I ran into him.
Wow.
There are 47 prefectures.
It's true.
Nagano Prefecture of 47 prefectures.
What?
I'm so happy.
As expected.
Thank you.
Oh, no.
Like this.
I'm on the second day now.
I'm still having fun!
It's so cold!
This guy is so thin!
Look at this.
I used it.
Look, he doesn't even have a scarf.
I've got all this stuff, too.
So here's to another year!
Let's go on another trip!
Let's go again this year!
We did, didn't we?
Yes, I did.
See you later.
Thank you very much.
I'm sure you've seen a lot of different people.
How was it?
I think everyone had a very relaxing time.
Now that we're in the middle of this year's distribution
I'm sure you two have a lot of things you want to do.
What do you want to do? Let's do something together.
I'd love to.
Well, it's a good thing we're here.
Since the three of us are here...
Shall we go on a trip?
I'd love to.
Saxanko?
Saxonoco's making a series.
Do you care?
I do.
I'd like to take a look around.
You're so thin back there.
You're thin back there.
I thought it'd be nice to walk together.
It would be nice to walk together.
It would be nice... if we could make it happen.
Please listen to me, Saxanko.
I'm sure you will.
I hope you'll enjoy this year's show as much as I did.
Lastly, please subscribe to our channel and give us a high rating!
Thank you very much.
Bye, bye, bye.
ED
Thank you for watching!